regalbuyer.com 2015-02-14

# Privacy Policy

At  **REGALBUYER** , we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about privacy and purchasing security. Therefore we have instituted policies to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly. We also have posted this privacy policy to let you know the type of information we collect, how it is handled and what choices you have regarding our use of your information.

**Is My Information Secure?**

We are committed to doing our best to maintain the security of information collected on our site. We have put in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Encryption is a process by which a message or information is scrambled while it is in transit for further processing. At  **REGALBUYER** , all of your personal information is protected

**What information do we collect?**

When you place an order from our web site, we may collect the following information in order to promptly and securely process your order: your name, telephone number, email address, billing information (credit card number, expiration date and billing address), shipping address, products purchased and promotional codes. (if any).

**How do we use customer information?**

We use information collected from you to process your orders and to email you special promotional offers and discounts from  **REGALBUYER**. We never share your personal information with any third party.

**Customer Protection**

REGALBUYER takes all measures to provide a safe environment with security procedures in place to ensure proper storage and careful retrieval of information so that nothing improper happens to your personal information while under our control.

**What we do with your information?**

Your privacy is a very sensitive subject for us and we take it very seriously. So our privacy policy is simple: we will not sell, barter, give away or rent your personal information to any third party outside of REGALBUYER and its properties. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will NOT include personal information of our customers.

**What are cookies?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser in your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. We may use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, record user specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to the site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads and customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about our Secure Shopping Policy or your personal experience dealing with this web site, you can contact us @  **08055260250 or enquiry@regalbuyer.com**
